Sashank Silwal

Web Developer at Cyber #

Email: ss13163@nyu.edu

Ever since I was a little kid, computer science has been my passion. I still remember writing my first code in QBASIC to print "Hello World" and being fascinated with it. It was almost magic, being able to get the computer to do whatever I wanted, just by typing in some lines of codes, limited only by my imagination and ingenuity. Throughout high school, I learned programming languages like C and Python and also Django framework to make basic websites.

This passion for computer science landed me as a student in the NYU Global Network.

Now, this passion remains with me. There's certainly yet more to learn, yet more problems to solve, and yet more to build. Specialties: Languages: Python, C++

EXPERIENCE

Cyber # NYUAD Jan 2020 to Present

Web Developer

Budhanilkantha Education Services

Jul 2019 to Sep 2019

Python tutor

EDUCATION

New York University Abu Dhabi

2019 to 2023

Bachelor of Science

Pursuing a Bachelor of Science. Majoring in Computer Science.

SKILLS

Python (Programming Language), Git, Programming, Non-profit Volunteering, Django, Adobe Illustrator, C++, HTML, Bootstrap

HONORS

Cambridge Outstanding Learner Awards

Top in the world award for Mathematics. Cambridge International Alevels

National Brainbox Quiz Winner

Certificate of higher distinction Australia Mathematics

LANGUAGES

English (Full professional proficiency)